<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rsi Prevention on StevenTammen.com</title>
    <link>https://www.steventammen.com/tags/rsi-prevention/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rsi Prevention on StevenTammen.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 18:03:28 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.steventammen.com/tags/rsi-prevention/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Work Environment</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/work-environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 18:03:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/work-environment/</guid>
      <description>Overview Your work environment is simply the collection of objects that play a role in your work. For most of us, that means a keyboard, a monitor, a desk, a chair, and some way to manage sound (headphones/earplugs). Each element of the work environment is briefly discussed below, but ultimately you should do more research. Don&#39;t just take my word for these things.
Keyboard Please have a look at this page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboards</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/keyboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:53:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/keyboards/</guid>
      <description>Good Options  Iris Keyboard Dactyl Keyboard Kinesis Advantage 2 Unikeyboard Diverge 3 ErgoDox EZ Let&#39;s Split  TODO Complete Outline  Optimization Considerations   Differences in Hand Morphology Differences in Optimization Goals (speed vs ergonomics)   Physical Layout Design Variables   Why Physical Layout Design Must Come Before Character Design Design Philosophy: Everything is a Variable Comfort/Ergonomics   Split-Hand Design Columnar Key Layout Adjustable Wrist Pronation (&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard Layouts</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/keyboard-layouts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:53:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/keyboard-layouts/</guid>
      <description>Tentative Eventual Structure For This Page  Pre-optimization Considerations   Reasons Why You Should Optimize   Reduced Typing Effort Reduced Risk of RSI Increased Typing Speed   Reasons Why You Should Not Optimize   Priorities You May Type Too Little For Optimization/Switching To Be Worth It You May Be Better Served By Learning Stenography The Difficulty of Retraining Your Fingers QWERTY&#39;s Ubiquitousness The Animosity of Others Most Speed Considerations Are Layout Agnostic   People Who Should Always Learn An Optimized Layout Prior Studies of Keyboard Layouts   Optimization Considerations   Differences in Hand Morphology   My Hand Morphology   Differences in Optimization Goals (speed vs ergonomics)   My Optimization Goals (balance)   Differences in Textual Corpus   My Textual Corpus (Latin, Greek, Hebrew, Markdown, Org, LaTeX, programming, number entry)   The Unavoidability of Opportunity Cost: Coming to an &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>