<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gear Cluster on StevenTammen.com</title>
    <link>https://www.steventammen.com/tags/gear-cluster/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gear Cluster on StevenTammen.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:58:06 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.steventammen.com/tags/gear-cluster/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rain Gear</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/rain-gear/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:58:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/rain-gear/</guid>
      <description>Waterproofing  Don&#39;t need it when it&#39;s not raining, extra unnecessary material   Additionally, want to be able to take off wet layers after rain ⇒ they should be separate Additionally, having waterproof/windproof shell separate from thermal layer means that it is more versatile and can be used across a wider temperature range than a single thermal layer that is waterproof/windproof. Argument could be made that it&#39;s one more jacket to carry around for cold, wet situations, but what if it is cold and rainy in the morning and hot and rainy in the afternoon?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every Day Carry</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/every-day-carry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:51:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/every-day-carry/</guid>
      <description>Distinction between Every Day Carry and Everyday Carry  This page is discussing the former, which includes the latter  Components  Essentials   Wallet Phone Keys Plain Edge Folder Multitool Flashlight Bandana   Keychain   Gorilla Tape Hardware Encrypted Flash Drive Yubikey Leatherman Squirt Keychain Light Bic Mini (and a waterproofing/tinder solution) Caffiene/L-Theanine Pills and emergency cash in a 2.6&#34; Go Tube. (Wrap with glow-in-the-dark tape). Safety pins   Cordage/Utility Materials   Locking Carabiner 600lb Technora Cord 200lb Kevlar 3-Strand Cord Velcro Ties Zip ties Ranger bands Binder Clips Superglue Scotch tape Masking tape Sharpie Ziploc bags   Writing Materials   Dot-Pad Notebook Sticky Notes 6&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clothing</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/clothing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:49:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/clothing/</guid>
      <description>Everyday Clothes  Shirt Belt Underwear Pants Vibram&#39;s KSO Evo Vibram&#39;s Trek Ascent Insulated (when it&#39;s too cold for the KSO&#39;s)  Dressy Clothes  Button-Down Shirt Underwear (same as above) Suit Toe Socks Dress Shoes  Work Clothes  Same shirt, belt, underwear and pants as everyday clothes Toe Socks (same as above) Second Sock Layer (worn to minimize rubbing) Work Boots  Exercise Clothes  Short Sleeve Baselayer Underwear (same as above) Cheap Synthetic Shorts Vibram&#39;s KSO Evo (same as above)  In Colder Weather, Add  Short Sleeve Baselayer Long Sleeve Baselayer Compression Calf Sleeves  TODO Other Section Ideas  Reason for cobra rigger&#39;s belt vs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>