<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on StevenTammen.com</title>
    <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on StevenTammen.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 18:04:31 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.steventammen.com/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Immaterial Things Worthy Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/immaterial-things-worthy-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 18:04:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/immaterial-things-worthy-projects/</guid>
      <description>Software Programs  Development of an open source, cross-platform keyboard program that supports key remapping, hotstrings, layers, macros, running programs through a hotstring/macro, opening URLs in the default browser through a hotstring/macro, and so forth. Also develop a spin-off project for implementing as meany features as possible on the firmware level. (Perhaps contributing to QMK firmware?) Development of an open source, cross-platform program to enable Vim/Spacemacs emulation across the entire operating system environment (configurable by .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Material Things Worthy Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/material-things-worthy-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 18:03:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/material-things-worthy-projects/</guid>
      <description>Physical Products  Development of an open source, split-hand, concacave, columnar, portable, ergonomic keyboard -- one that takes design cues from the Dactyl Keyboard while slimming down the number of keys and adding built-in adjustability. Try to get an assembly/distribution service of some sort in place to bring ergonomic, split-hand, concave keyboards to the masses. Development of an open source, ergonomic, finger-controlled trackball that allows for a perfectly straight wrist and low pronation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work Environment</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/work-environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 18:03:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/work-environment/</guid>
      <description>Overview Your work environment is simply the collection of objects that play a role in your work. For most of us, that means a keyboard, a monitor, a desk, a chair, and some way to manage sound (headphones/earplugs). Each element of the work environment is briefly discussed below, but ultimately you should do more research. Don&#39;t just take my word for these things.
Keyboard Please have a look at this page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watches</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/watches/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 18:02:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/watches/</guid>
      <description>Watch Type  Analog watches superior for telling relative time But digital watches have desirable features like stopwatches, timers, day/date, world time, alarms, etc. Therefore, analog-digital watches make sense  Case  Reasonably impact resistant, chemical resistant, magnetic resistant, temperature resistant, pressure resistant/water resistant. Balance good specs with price and use case. Make the lugs about as wide as the watch face (i.e., don&#39;t add width), the thicker the watch band material, the more it distributes pressure on the wrist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screen Reading</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/screen-reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 18:01:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/screen-reading/</guid>
      <description>Recommended Reading General print vs screens  http://www.newyorker.com/science/maria-konnikova/being-a-better-online-reader https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/reading-paper-screens/ https://www.wired.com/2014/05/reading-on-screen-versus-paper/ https://www.lezen.nl/sites/default/files/On%20reading%20in%20the%20digital%20age.pdf http://www.academia.edu/2244249/Mangen_A._2008_._Hypertext_fiction_reading_haptics_and_immersion http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0883035512001127 http://scholarworks.sjsu.edu/cgi/viewcontent.cgi?article=1186&amp;context=slissrj http://www.cdmc.ucla.edu/PG_Media_biblio_files/A250%20Subrahmanyam%20Michikyan%20et%20al%202014%20(paper%20vs%20screens)%5B1%5D.pdf http://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/00220973.2016.1143794?src=recsys https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=8882481  Cognitive maps  https://www.researchgate.net/publication/309562571_Cognitive_map_or_medium_materiality_Reading_on_paper_and_screen http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1071581905001722  My Hypotheses and Thoughts Cognitive Maps Cognitive maps are the determinative factor in organizing information efficiently (leading to better short term operational capacity and better long term memory encoding). When taking in information, we want to make it easiest to form cognitive maps. Some guidelines:
 Display two pages side by side like in print.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rain Gear</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/rain-gear/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:58:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/rain-gear/</guid>
      <description>Waterproofing  Don&#39;t need it when it&#39;s not raining, extra unnecessary material   Additionally, want to be able to take off wet layers after rain ⇒ they should be separate Additionally, having waterproof/windproof shell separate from thermal layer means that it is more versatile and can be used across a wider temperature range than a single thermal layer that is waterproof/windproof. Argument could be made that it&#39;s one more jacket to carry around for cold, wet situations, but what if it is cold and rainy in the morning and hot and rainy in the afternoon?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Priorities</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/priorities/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:57:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/priorities/</guid>
      <description>Limited Time An axiom of existence is the limited nature of time. With normal life responsibilities, there are only so many things that we can spend time on. The more we build discipline and focus, the more we can get to, given our particular set of circumstances. But we will never be able to get to everything. It is necessary that we decide on a method for determining what we focus on, and structure our lives from most important to least important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pencils</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/pencils/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:57:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/pencils/</guid>
      <description>Basic Idea  From a practical standpoint, mechanical pencils are better than wood pencils (worst) and leadholders (not quite as bad, but suboptimal for everyday use outside of a few specific applications). You have to sharpen wood pencils, and you get wood shavings as well as lead shavings. Additionally, if you are writing with a soft lead (as you should be), it will dull very quickly and you will have to sharpen often.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pencil Leads</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/pencil-leads/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:57:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/pencil-leads/</guid>
      <description>Lead Grade  Higher softness is better: darker line, writes more smoothly, takes less pressure to deposit graphite on the page. Disadvantages: Smudges easier (especially bad if you&#39;re a lefty) Lead comparison: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=73gZFjIAHtw  Lead Width  While it is true that wider leads are smoother (ever try pushing a needle across a piece of paper?), if we posit that lead softness is the main determiner of smoothness, then the net effect is probably small enough that advantages of thinner lead should not be sacrificed for very marginal gains in smoothness ⇒ the lead width should be as large as possible while taking into account the following considerations:   Smaller lead width is better in terms of darkness: the same amount of pressure over a smaller area will lead to a greater force, and more graphite on the page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pants</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/pants/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:56:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/pants/</guid>
      <description>Always wearing pants  Long pants provide abrasion resistance, water resistance, and sun protection to the legs. Having abrasion resistance on the full length of the legs is useful (rather than just the top). Long pants also help protect against bugs and wind. Long Pants and Safety  Pockets  Pants without pockets are silly. Pockets come in useful for carrying things around day-to-day and also for storing things temporarily if you need too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multitools</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/multitools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:56:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/multitools/</guid>
      <description>Discussed Models LM = Leatherman Charge TTI Vic = Victorinox SwissTool Spirit Leatherman Squirt PS4
LM Pros  One-handed opening blades S30v steel True needle nose pliers that open wide A Diamond file that can be used to sharpen stuff and handle hard materials Wider opening scissors More sharply machined screwdrivers (that are much less likely to slip) Better wire cutters A pocket clip that is one of the best available on any pocket knife.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motorcycles</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/motorcycles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:56:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/motorcycles/</guid>
      <description>Safety  Motorcycles are inherently more dangerous than cars due to no barrier between you and other (sometimes incompetent) motorists driving 2-ton metal cages. On the other hand, motorcycles are inherently safer than cars due to 1) better vision (higher up on bikes with upright seating position, no blind spots, can easily head-check), 2) better acceleration, maneuverability, and handling, 3) better attention forced by being more &#34;present&#34; in the act of driving, and 4) better risk awareness: motorcycles make you assume less about your safety and therefore take less risks/be more risk conscious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitors</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/monitors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:56:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/monitors/</guid>
      <description>Essential Features  OLED 4k resolution At least a 60 Hz refresh rate Capable of of 4:4:4 chroma 40+ inches Ability to sleep without messing with windows Low input lag  Preferable Features  Curved (to better fill field of vision at close distances) Smart TV functionality/has remote Modes dependent upon activity (e.g., TV, gaming, etc.). Be able to customize modes.  4k vs Multiple HD Monitors  Having one large 4k monitor lets you use the monitor as a TV It also avoids unecessary bezels in normal computing tasks Assuming you have a good tiling window manager, the ease of laying out windows should not be significantly different between the two configurations  Size and Resolution  Increased screen size without matching increases in resolution has diminishing returns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Purpose</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/life-purpose/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:54:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/life-purpose/</guid>
      <description>Argument 1: Objective morality exists Strict materialists often argue that existence is actually futile and that the meaningfulness of life is a charade that we keep up to numb ourselves to the coldness of reality. Under such a supposition, morality is seen through a subjective lens, a human construct propogated by the weak to keep the strong from ruling them absolutely. There is no right and wrong because the universe is governed by uncaring natural laws and humans are merely strings of predictable biological cause and effect drifting to and fro by chance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Styles</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/learning-styles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:53:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/learning-styles/</guid>
      <description>Print as Superior Medium for Information Transmission  Almost all people read faster than they can comfortably listen to someone speak. (Ever try reading the transcript of a podcast and then listening to it at 2.5x speed? It should make what I&#39;m talking about obvious). Reading is also much faster than taking in most types of complex/overly difficult information in some sort of visual form (e.g., a table).   It&#39;s also worth pointing out that nothing stops writers from including charts, graphs, pictures, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboards</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/keyboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:53:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/keyboards/</guid>
      <description>Good Options  Iris Keyboard Dactyl Keyboard Kinesis Advantage 2 Unikeyboard Diverge 3 ErgoDox EZ Let&#39;s Split  TODO Complete Outline  Optimization Considerations   Differences in Hand Morphology Differences in Optimization Goals (speed vs ergonomics)   Physical Layout Design Variables   Why Physical Layout Design Must Come Before Character Design Design Philosophy: Everything is a Variable Comfort/Ergonomics   Split-Hand Design Columnar Key Layout Adjustable Wrist Pronation (&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard Layouts</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/keyboard-layouts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:53:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/keyboard-layouts/</guid>
      <description>Tentative Eventual Structure For This Page  Pre-optimization Considerations   Reasons Why You Should Optimize   Reduced Typing Effort Reduced Risk of RSI Increased Typing Speed   Reasons Why You Should Not Optimize   Priorities You May Type Too Little For Optimization/Switching To Be Worth It You May Be Better Served By Learning Stenography The Difficulty of Retraining Your Fingers QWERTY&#39;s Ubiquitousness The Animosity of Others Most Speed Considerations Are Layout Agnostic   People Who Should Always Learn An Optimized Layout Prior Studies of Keyboard Layouts   Optimization Considerations   Differences in Hand Morphology   My Hand Morphology   Differences in Optimization Goals (speed vs ergonomics)   My Optimization Goals (balance)   Differences in Textual Corpus   My Textual Corpus (Latin, Greek, Hebrew, Markdown, Org, LaTeX, programming, number entry)   The Unavoidability of Opportunity Cost: Coming to an &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keto</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/keto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:52:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/keto/</guid>
      <description>About Ketosis  http://eatingacademy.com/nutrition/ketosis-advantaged-or-misunderstood-state-part-i http://eatingacademy.com/nutrition/ketosis-advantaged-or-misunderstood-state-part-ii http://eatingacademy.com/sports-and-nutrition/ketones-carbohydrates-can-co-exist http://eatingacademy.com/nutrition/the-interplay-of-exercise-and-ketosis-part-i http://eatingacademy.com/nutrition/the-interplay-of-exercise-and-ketosis-part-ii https://www.amazon.com/Art-Science-Low-Carbohydrate-Living/dp/0983490708/ https://www.amazon.com/Art-Science-Low-Carbohydrate-Performance/dp/0983490716/  Starting List of Foods  Meat   Beef sausage patties, ground beef, steaks/stew meats, liverwurst; chicken breasts; bacon; lamb; salmon and sardines; bone broth/gelatin   Other Core Foods   Coconut oil; EVOO; butter and ghee; eggs; avocados; almond butter   Vegetables   Broccoli, cauliflower, Brussels sprouts, kale, spinach, arugula, bok choy, cabbage, swiss chard, asparagus, celery, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guns</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/guns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:52:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/guns/</guid>
      <description>Caliber  9mm for compromise between weight, capacity, muzzle velocity (less drop at distance) Jacketed Hollow Point (JHP) rounds nullify many of the advantages that .45 has over 9mm, namely, less overpenetration and wider wound paths (more stopping power). Cheaper for plinking  Frame  Want a double stack for capacity. Makes EDCing a spare mag uneccessary (plus not having to change for more shots is faster than having to change).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Material Things Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/material-things-evaluation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:52:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/material-things-evaluation/</guid>
      <description>Variables  There will be different variables for different items. The first step when researching a particular item or class of item should always be the identification of variables that will be important to optimize around. You will also want to identify the specifics of your particular use case, and weight variables accordingly. &#34;Best&#34; is relative to what the item will be used for -- a really good pair of tactical cargo pants probably won&#39;t be the best pants to go with your suit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fabrics</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/fabrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:51:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/fabrics/</guid>
      <description>TODO Fabric Properties Heat Transfer basics  http://www.sjsu.edu/people/craig.cisar/courses/kin256/s1/LEC-2-rev09---Therm-Env-and-Cloth-.ppt  General Fabric Characteristics  http://blog.outdoorherbivore.com/camp-tips/clothing/ http://snarkynomad.com/why-merino-wool-t-shirts-are-the-best-travel-t-shirts/ http://www.survivalistboards.com/showthread.php?t=79756  Wool Vs. Synthetics  https://backpackinglight.com/comfort_moisture_transport_wool_synthetic_clothing/  Overstated Claims Of Wicking Fabrics  http://hprc-online.org/blog/is-wicking-apparel-as-201ccool201d-as-you-think http://scholarworks.wmich.edu/cgi/viewcontent.cgi?article=1190&amp;context=masters_theses http://www.ayfcoaching.com/AcuCustom/Sitename/Documents/DocumentItem/04Kicklighter.pdf  Tencel  http://www.thetextilethinktank.org/important-properties-tencel-fibers/ http://www.academia.edu/8619889/COMFORT_AND_PROTECTION_PROPERTIES_OF_TENCEL_COTTON_BLENDS http://www.academia.edu/26251973/AN_OVERVIEW_ON_THE_INFLUENCE_OF_FABRIC_STRUCTURAL_PARAMETERS_IN_SPORTS_INTIMATE_APPARELS http://bushcraftusa.com/forum/threads/tencel-lyocell-fabric.182558/  Clothing Color And Thermoregulation  http://io9.gizmodo.com/5903956/the-physics-that-explain-why-you-should-wear-black-this-summer http://physics.stackexchange.com/questions/78616/is-dark-clothes-for-winter-light-for-summer-relevant#101204  Merino Wool Vs. Alpaca Shape Retention  http://snarkynomad.com/why-merino-wool-t-shirts-are-the-best-travel-t-shirts/ (comments: ctrl-f: &#34;alpaca&#34;) https://backpackinglight.com/forums/topic/81962/ Alpaca does not have the extreme bending strength that Merino has, and so can loose its shape/form easier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every Day Carry</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/every-day-carry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:51:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/every-day-carry/</guid>
      <description>Distinction between Every Day Carry and Everyday Carry  This page is discussing the former, which includes the latter  Components  Essentials   Wallet Phone Keys Plain Edge Folder Multitool Flashlight Bandana   Keychain   Gorilla Tape Hardware Encrypted Flash Drive Yubikey Leatherman Squirt Keychain Light Bic Mini (and a waterproofing/tinder solution) Caffiene/L-Theanine Pills and emergency cash in a 2.6&#34; Go Tube. (Wrap with glow-in-the-dark tape). Safety pins   Cordage/Utility Materials   Locking Carabiner 600lb Technora Cord 200lb Kevlar 3-Strand Cord Velcro Ties Zip ties Ranger bands Binder Clips Superglue Scotch tape Masking tape Sharpie Ziploc bags   Writing Materials   Dot-Pad Notebook Sticky Notes 6&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Erasers</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/erasers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:50:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/erasers/</guid>
      <description>Recommended Reading  http://smbhax.com/cgi-bin/newsarchive.pl?p=1197 http://smbhax.com/cgi-bin/newsarchive.pl?p=1205 http://smbhax.com/cgi-bin/newsarchive.pl?p=1207 http://www.wellappointeddesk.com/2016/07/the-great-eraser-rub-off-challenge/ https://theweeklypencil.com/2016/03/22/eraser-round-up/ http://www.comic-tools.com/2009/08/this-week-eraser-rub-off-howdy-comic.html http://www.jetpens.com/profile/viewReviews?id=f2d07c0462ceee46 http://robotninjamonsters.blogspot.com/2009/07/pentel-hi-polymer-eraser-review-and.html https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jZaNDG7Vk1c  Foam Erasers, Sakura Arch Sleeve Design  https://www.reddit.com/r/pencils/comments/3qcy6i/finally_my_favorite_eraser_has_arrived/ http://www.jetpens.com/Sakura-Foam-Eraser-W-100/pd/13188/related http://www.jetpens.com/Sakura-Arch-Foam-Eraser-60/pd/13750/related https://disqus.com/home/discussion/jetpensblog/a_guide_to_erasers/ https://eastwesteverywhere.wordpress.com/2015/05/16/sakura-arch-foam-eraser/ http://comfortableshoesstudio.com/review-mitsubishi-boxy-eraser/ http://comfortableshoesstudio.com/review-sakura-super-foam-eraser/  Detail work  https://www.amazon.com/Tombow-MONO-Eraser-Round-1-Pack/dp/B005IQHCHK https://www.amazon.com/Tombow-MONO-Eraser-Rectangle-1-Pack/dp/B005IQHCKM/  Shading and art stuff  kneaded eraser  My Picks  Kokuyo Campus Student Eraser - For 2B Lead  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Letterforms</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/english-letterforms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:50:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/english-letterforms/</guid>
      <description>Cursive Vs. Print  Because everything in print uses uses print letterforms, in our day and age, we are more accustomed to reading print letters than cursive letters. Just think about it logically: if most of what we read uses print letterforms, it just makes intuitive sense that we will be more used to reading them, and therefore faster and better at recognizing them. (I.e., they will be more legible to us).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dictionary Generator</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/dictionary-generator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:49:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/dictionary-generator/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer I have been watching Plover for a long time, but haven&#39;t actually learned very much steno yet (at least physically). Part of this is because the SOFT/HRUF is still yet to ship, and part of it also is because I have been very busy. What I&#39;m trying to say is that my comments should be taken with a large helping of salt. It is entirely possible that there are things in the software that I&#39;m not aware of or am misinformed about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clothing</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/clothing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:49:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/clothing/</guid>
      <description>Everyday Clothes  Shirt Belt Underwear Pants Vibram&#39;s KSO Evo Vibram&#39;s Trek Ascent Insulated (when it&#39;s too cold for the KSO&#39;s)  Dressy Clothes  Button-Down Shirt Underwear (same as above) Suit Toe Socks Dress Shoes  Work Clothes  Same shirt, belt, underwear and pants as everyday clothes Toe Socks (same as above) Second Sock Layer (worn to minimize rubbing) Work Boots  Exercise Clothes  Short Sleeve Baselayer Underwear (same as above) Cheap Synthetic Shorts Vibram&#39;s KSO Evo (same as above)  In Colder Weather, Add  Short Sleeve Baselayer Long Sleeve Baselayer Compression Calf Sleeves  TODO Other Section Ideas  Reason for cobra rigger&#39;s belt vs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backpacks</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/backpacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:49:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/backpacks/</guid>
      <description>Optimization Variables TODO: determine best order to go through variables. Alphabetically?
TODO: decide if having some sort of weighting scheme would be appropriate, or if leaving it to individuals and their circumstances would be better.
Sweat Management When wearing a backpack for an extended period of time, especially on hot and humid days, it is best to have some way to minimize pack contact with your back. Failing to have such a system leads to excessive sweat buildup, and, over time, smell.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>