<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Edc on StevenTammen.com</title>
    <link>https://www.steventammen.com/tags/edc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Edc on StevenTammen.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 18:02:19 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.steventammen.com/tags/edc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Watches</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/watches/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 18:02:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/watches/</guid>
      <description>Watch Type  Analog watches superior for telling relative time But digital watches have desirable features like stopwatches, timers, day/date, world time, alarms, etc. Therefore, analog-digital watches make sense  Case  Reasonably impact resistant, chemical resistant, magnetic resistant, temperature resistant, pressure resistant/water resistant. Balance good specs with price and use case. Make the lugs about as wide as the watch face (i.e., don&#39;t add width), the thicker the watch band material, the more it distributes pressure on the wrist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multitools</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/multitools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:56:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/multitools/</guid>
      <description>Discussed Models LM = Leatherman Charge TTI Vic = Victorinox SwissTool Spirit Leatherman Squirt PS4
LM Pros  One-handed opening blades S30v steel True needle nose pliers that open wide A Diamond file that can be used to sharpen stuff and handle hard materials Wider opening scissors More sharply machined screwdrivers (that are much less likely to slip) Better wire cutters A pocket clip that is one of the best available on any pocket knife.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every Day Carry</title>
      <link>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/every-day-carry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:51:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steventammen.com/pages/every-day-carry/</guid>
      <description>Distinction between Every Day Carry and Everyday Carry  This page is discussing the former, which includes the latter  Components  Essentials   Wallet Phone Keys Plain Edge Folder Multitool Flashlight Bandana   Keychain   Gorilla Tape Hardware Encrypted Flash Drive Yubikey Leatherman Squirt Keychain Light Bic Mini (and a waterproofing/tinder solution) Caffiene/L-Theanine Pills and emergency cash in a 2.6&#34; Go Tube. (Wrap with glow-in-the-dark tape). Safety pins   Cordage/Utility Materials   Locking Carabiner 600lb Technora Cord 200lb Kevlar 3-Strand Cord Velcro Ties Zip ties Ranger bands Binder Clips Superglue Scotch tape Masking tape Sharpie Ziploc bags   Writing Materials   Dot-Pad Notebook Sticky Notes 6&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>